<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photography on Fundi Willy&#39;s Low-Level Electronics Lab</title>
    <link>https://wilfred.githuka.com/categories/photography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photography on Fundi Willy&#39;s Low-Level Electronics Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 19:40:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wilfred.githuka.com/categories/photography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LifeLog 2017 Edition Day 90 Update</title>
      <link>https://wilfred.githuka.com/post/lifelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 19:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wilfred.githuka.com/post/lifelog/</guid>
      <description>Today is Friday, the 31st of March, 2017. There are 275 days, 6,604 hours and more that 400,000 minutes left for the year to come to an end. We are 90 days into 2018 and its already feels long enough. When the year comes to a close many will say that year went fast, and almost cannot recall most days of the year due to us having countless activies in a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiking At Ngong Hills With Ruaraka Baptist Church Teens</title>
      <link>https://wilfred.githuka.com/post/hiking-at-ngong-hills/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 08:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wilfred.githuka.com/post/hiking-at-ngong-hills/</guid>
      <description>Located SW of Nairobi is Kenya&#39;s largest Wind Farm, Ngong Hills. The word &amp;ldquo;Ngong&amp;quot;as I was told by the locals is an Anglicization of a Maasai phrase &amp;ldquo;enkong&#39;u emuny&amp;rdquo; meaning rhinoceros spring, and this name derives from a spring located near Ngong Town. Overlooking the Great Rift Valey on the Western Slopes, the Nong Hills rise to 2,460 meters above sea level.During the years of British colonial rule, the area around the Ngong Hills was a major settler farming region, and many traditional colonial houses are still seen in the area.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>