<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Elecrical Engineering on Fundi Willy&#39;s Low-Level Electronics Lab</title>
    <link>https://wilfred.githuka.com/categories/elecrical-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Elecrical Engineering on Fundi Willy&#39;s Low-Level Electronics Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 13:56:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wilfred.githuka.com/categories/elecrical-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up A Linode VPS Virtual Private Server</title>
      <link>https://wilfred.githuka.com/post/my-linode-vps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 13:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wilfred.githuka.com/post/my-linode-vps/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Finally after fiddling up with some settings, my Linode VPS is running perfectly. Before going deeper let me explain what is a VPS. A VPS is a Virtual Private Server that is esentially a computer in a dfferent location where you can install programs while having access to it via SSH or other protocols. A VPS (Virtual Private Server) is utilised by businesses looking for a secure method of hosting their websites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Week In My Engineering Career</title>
      <link>https://wilfred.githuka.com/post/twimec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 00:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wilfred.githuka.com/post/twimec/</guid>
      <description>▲ We use oscillators in most of our experiments, perfect tool for ciruit analysis.
EEE 309 Analogue Electronics 2 Labwork This week&#39;s labwork was about an introduction to Op-Amps. We worked with the UA741CN Chip Op-Amp. The experiment was good but I still think I need to get myself a chip and see how it really works.On a better note the Digital Electronics practical on &amp;ldquo;Digital Counter With 7 Segment Display&amp;rdquo; was a success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Driving Car Project - Part 1 Project Update</title>
      <link>https://wilfred.githuka.com/post/self-driving-rc-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 22:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wilfred.githuka.com/post/self-driving-rc-car/</guid>
      <description>▲ Current state of the car as of May 3rd 2017
This week has been very busy for me since I started making my self driving car model out of an RC Car. Last year I got a Red Hammer H2 RC Car. This car is made in China on a Ratio of 1:14 and runs on 5x1.5V .The project is simple, make it drive itself and learn alot of stuff while at it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>